Guide to the The New Leader Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Artwork, 1928-2006, undated
  - Subseries V. 1: Artwork by Subject, 1961-2006, undated
    - HE-HI, 1965-2005, undated (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Hitler, Adolf, undated (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - HJ-HZ, 1964-2005, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 136, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Hoover, Herbert, undated (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Humphrey, Hubert, 1967-1972, undated (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Hussein, King, 1970, undated (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Hussein, Saddam, 1990-2003, undated (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - I, 1963-1990, undated (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - International Organizations, 1963-2005, undated (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - JA, 1969-1992, undated (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Jackson, Jesse, 1984, undated (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Jaruzelski, Wojciech, 1990, undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - JE-JZ, 1966-1995, undated (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Jefferson, Thomas, undated (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., undated (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - K-KE, 1962-2004, undated (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, Edward, 1966-1980, undated (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy, John and Jackie, 1963-2006, undated (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Kennedy, Robert, 1968, undated (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - KF-KI, 1967-2005, undated (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Kim Dae Jung, 2005, undated (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1972-2004, undated (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - KJ-KZ, 1967-1999, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 138, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Kohl, Helmut, 1990-1995, undated (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Krushchev, Nikita, 1986, undated (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - L, 1965-2005, undated (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - L, 1965-2005, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 139, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Lenin, Vladimir I., undated (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Levitas, Sol, 19 March 1961 (Drawing by [J. Bannejee, Calcutta]) (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - MA-MC, 1965-2004, undated, (3 Folders) (Box 139, Folder 5 to 7)
    - MA-MC, 1965-2004, undated (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Major, John, 1992-1995, undated (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Mao Tse-Tung, 1962-1970, undated (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - McGovern, George, undated (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - MD-MI, 1981-2005, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 140, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Mitterand, Francois, 1970, undated (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - MJ-MO, 1968-1993, undated (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Mondale, Walter, undated (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1970-1990, undated (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - MU-MZ, 1980-1993, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 141, Folder 1 to 2)
    - N, 1968-1990, undated, (3 Folders) (Box 141, Folder 3 to 5)
    - Nixon, Richard, 1969-1990, undated (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - O, 1965-1994, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 141, Folder 7 to 8)
    - Ortega, Daniel, 1989-1990, undated (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - PA-PI, 1971-2001, undated (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - PA-PI, 1971-2001, undated, (3 Folders) (Box 142, Folder 2 to 4)
    - Peres, Shimon, 1987-1993, undated (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - PJ-PZ, 1963-2001, undated, (3 Folders) (Box 142, Folder 6 to 8)
    - Pope John Paul I, 1992, undated (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Q, 1986-undated (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - RA, 1971-2001, undated (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Rabin, Yitzchak, 1989-2001, undated (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - RE-RN, 1963-1977, undated (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Reagan, Nancy and Ronald, 1967-2004, undated (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - RO, 1965-2006, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 143, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor and Franklin, undated (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1971, undated (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - RU, 1965-2006, undated (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - S-SA, 1966-2005, undated (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Sadat, Anwar, 1971-1993, undated (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - SB-SH, 1965-2005, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 144, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Shamir, Yitzchak, undated (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Sharon, Ariel, 2001-2003, undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Shevardnadze, Eduard, 1988-1989, undated (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Shultz, George P., 1973-1988, undated (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - SI-SM, 1966-1998, undated (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - SO-SZ, 1965-2005, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 145, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Stalin, Joseph, 1989-2005, undated (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Stevenson, Adlai, undated (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - TA-TI, 1962-2005, undated (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Thatcher, Margaret, 1982-1993, undated (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Tito, Josef, 1967-1968, undated (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - TJ-TZ, 1961-2006, undated (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Truman, Harry, undated (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - U, 1965-1993, undated (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified buildings and scenes, 1957, undated (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified military, 1967-1984, undated (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified people, 1979, undated (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - V, 1965-1994, undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - W-WE, 1962-1993, undated (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Walesa, Lech, 1989-1990, undated (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Wallace, George, 1968-1972, undated (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Warren, Earl, 1964-1970 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - WF-WZ, 1965-1997, undated (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Wiesel, Elie, undated (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Harold, undated, 1964-1990 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - XYZ, 1962-1994, undated (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Yeltsin, Boris, 1993, undated (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Zhao Ziyang, undated (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Countries--United States
      - Agriculture, 1976-1989, undated (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Buildings--Monuments and Cities--Non-government, 1972, undated (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - Buildings--Monuments and Cities--Washington, D.C., 1986-2005, undated (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - Politics--Conceptual and Cartoons--Scenes, 1969-2004, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 148, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Defense, 1961-1986, undated (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Demonstrations, 1969, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 148, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Economics--Conceptual, 1970-1993, undated (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Economy Scenes, 1984-1986, undated (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - Education--Higher, 1969, undated (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Education--Lower, undated (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - Health, 1969-1975, undated (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - Industry, Labor, and Technology, 1965-2003, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 149, Folder 6 to 7)
      - Justice--Courts and Police, 1973, undated (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - Poverty and U.S. Elderly, 1968-1986, undated (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - Race, 1970, undated (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - Society and Scenes, 1970-1995, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 150, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Countries--Other
      - Africa, 1963-1995, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 151, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Australia, undated (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - Britain, 1962-2004, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 151, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Canada, 1993, undated (Box 151, Folder 6)
      - Caribbean, 1963-1994, undated (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - China I, 1964-1990, undated (Box 151, Folder 8)
      - China II, 1964-1990, undated (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - Cuba, 1963-1965, undated (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - Eastern Europe, 1961-1993, undated (Box 152, Folder 3)
      - France, 1984-2004, undated (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Germany--West and Austria, 1961-1985, undated (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - Greece, undated (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - India, 1966-1993, undated (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - Ireland, 1980, undated (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Israel, 1967-2004, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 153, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Italy and Vatican, 1988, undated (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - Japan, 1961-1993, undated (Box 153, Folder 5)
      - Latin America, 1965-1993, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 153, Folder 6 to 7)
      - Mexico, undated (Box 153, Folder 8)
      - Middle East, 1969-1990, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 154, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Portugal, 1965, undated (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - Spain, 1967-1989, undated (Box 154, Folder 4)
      - Southeast Asia, 1970-1994, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 154, Folder 5 to 6)
      - Soviet Union, 1987-1994, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 154, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Turkey, 1963 undated (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Subseries V. 2: Artwork--General, 1928-1975, undated
    Subseries 2 includes work often related to mechanicals or design.
    - Books Issue Mechanicals--Michael Aron and Co., undated (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Bressler, G.--NYPL Exhibit--Unused, undated (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Covers, 15 October 1961, (2 Folders) (Box 155, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Design Awards, 1973-1975 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - [Elwan, E.S.]--NYPL Exhibit, undated (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Geller, Barry--NYPL Exhibit, August 1964 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Herb Lubalin Redesign--First Issue, 18 September 1961 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Issue, 22 May 1961 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Photostated Headlines, undated (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Promotional Mechanicals, undated (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Special Issue Mechanicals, undated (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Young, Art--This 1928 Campaign in Cartoons, 1928, (3 Folders) (Box 155, Folder 13 to 15)
  - Subseries V. 3: Artwork--Oversized--by Subject, 1961-2006, undated
    Subseries 3 includes oversized artwork depicting many of the same subjects of Subseries 1. The pieces are organized by subject and often unsigned and undated.
    - General
      - A, 1964-2006, undated (Box 156, Folder 1)
      - The Arts, undated (Box 156, Folder 2)
      - B, 1962-2005, undated (Box 156, Folder 3)
      - C, 1961-1995, undated (Box 156, Folder 4)
      - Carter, Jimmy, undated (Box 156, Folder 5)
      - Clinton, Bill and Hillary, undated (Box 156, Folder 6)
      - D, 1968-2005, undated (Box 156, Folder 7)
      - E-FZ, 1961-2003, undated (Box 156, Folder 8)
      - Ford, Gerald, undated (Box 156, Folder 9)
      - G, 1967, undated (Box 157, Folder 1)
      - Gorbachev, Mikhail, 1984-1988, undated (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - GP-GZ, 1967, 1996, undated (Box 157, Folder 3)
      - H-JA, 1970-1984, undated (Box 157, Folder 4)
      - Holocaust Museum, 1993 (Box 157, Folder 5)
      - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1968, undated (Box 157, Folder 6)
      - K, undated (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - Kerouac, Jack, undated (Box 157, Folder 8)
      - King, Martin Luther, Jr., undated (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - L, undated (Box 157, Folder 10)
      - M, 1962-1994, undated (Box 157, Folder 11)
      - N, 1963, undated (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - Nixon, Richard, undated (Box 158, Folder 2)
      - PA-PI, 1984, undated (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - PJ-PZ, 1964, undated (Box 158, Folder 4)
      - R, undated (Box 158, Folder 5)
      - Reagan, Ronald, undated (Box 158, Folder 6)
      - S, 1966-1985, undated (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - TA-TI, 1962, undated (Box 158, Folder 8)
      - T, undated (Box 158, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified--General, 1957-1984, undated (Box 158, Folder 10)
      - United Nations, 1965-1997, undated (Box 158, Folder 11)
      - U-V, 1965-1969, undated (Box 158, Folder 12)
      - W, 1962, undated (Box 159, Folder 1)
      - Wilson, Woodrow, 1967, undated (Box 159, Folder 2)
      - Yeltsin, Boris, 1993, undated (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - XYZ, 1972, undated (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Countries--United States
      - Agriculture, 1976-1989, undated (Box 159, Folder 5)
      - Buildings, Monuments and City Scenes, 1972-2005, undated (Box 159, Folder 6)
      - Politics--Conceptual and Cartoons--Scenes, 1969-2004, undated (Box 159, Folder 7)
      - Defense, 1961-1986, undated (Box 159, Folder 8)
      - Economics--Conceptual, 1970-1993, undated (Box 159, Folder 9)
      - Economy Scenes, 1984-1986, undated (Box 159, Folder 10)
      - Education, 1969, undated (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - Health, undated (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Industry, Labor and Technology, undated (Box 160, Folder 3)
      - Justice--Courts and Police, undated (Box 160, Folder 4)
      - Poverty and U.S. Elderly, undated (Box 160, Folder 5)
      - Race, 1962-1967, undated (Box 160, Folder 6)
      - Society and Scenes, 1984, undated (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Countries--Other
      - Africa, 1963, undated (Box 160, Folder 8)
      - Britain, undated (Box 160, Folder 9)
      - China, 1973-1989, undated (Box 160, Folder 10)
      - Cuba, 1965, undated (Box 161, Folder 1)
      - Eastern Europe, 1961-1967, undated (Box 161, Folder 2)
      - France, undated (Box 161, Folder 3)
      - Germany--West and Austria, 1966-1977, undated (Box 161, Folder 4)
      - Israel, 2002, undated (Box 161, Folder 5)
      - Latin America, 1965-1969 (Box 161, Folder 6)
      - Middle East, undated (Box 161, Folder 7)
      - Netherlands, undated (Box 161, Folder 8)
      - Spain, undated (Box 161, Folder 9)
      - Southeast Asia, 1985-1994, undated (Box 161, Folder 10)
      - Soviet Union, undated (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Subseries V. 4: Artwork and Covers--Oversized--by Artist, 1961-1998, undated
    Subseries 4 includes oversized artwork that is more often signed than titled; it is organized by artist, by date within artist, and by size. Cover art is noted as such in the folder title.
    - Ackerman, Stan--Untitled, 1971 (Folder MD)
    - [Ackeriyan]--George McGovern, June 26, 1972 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - B. Bailer, B.--Covers
      - John V. Lindsay, 7 July 1969 (Box 162, Folder 2)
      - Untitled, 10 August 1969 (Box 162, Folder 3)
      - Le Duan, 15 September 1969 (Box 162, Folder 4)
      - Untitled, Undated (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - [Barhesto]--Marshal Tito, September 16, 1963 cover (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Beck, Jack Wolfgang, untitled, undated (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Bendis, Keith--Untitled, undated (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Bennett, Richard--Untitled--Cover, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 167, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Berg Victor, Joan
      - Untitled, 28 February 28, 1962 (Box 162, Folder 8)
      - Charles de Gaulle--Cover, 2 April 1962 (Box 162, Folder 9)
      - Untitled--Cover, undated (Box 162, Folder 10)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Berg Victor, Joan--Untitled, undated (Box 167, Folder 4)
      - Untitled--Cover, 8 June 8, 1964 (Box 162, Folder 12)
      - Untitled--Cover, undated (Box 162, Folder 13)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Biamonte, D.--Jimmy Carter, undated (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - Bressler, G.--Untitled, undated (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Brickner, Alice--Untitled--Cover, 31 May 1971 (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - [Burey, Ev]--Untitled, 13 November 1961 (Box 162, Folder 18)
    - Chang, Michelle--Untitled--Cover, undated (Box 162, Folder 19)
    - [Chuvurst]--Untitled, undated (Box 162, Folder 20)
    - [Ciller]--Untitled, undated (Box 162, Folder 21)
    - Dauphin, Georges--Russians in Afghanistan--Cover, December 1979 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - DeVoto, Joe--Untitled, undated (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Fernandez, Julio
      - Untitled, 1967 (Box 162, Folder 22)
      - LBJ--Cover, 24 April 1967 (Box 162, Folder 23)
      - Untitled--Cover, April 1968 (Box 162, Folder 24)
      - Truong Dinh Dzu--Cover, 5 August 1968 (Box 162, Folder 25)
      - Aswan Dam, undated (Box 162, Folder 26)
      - Untitled--Cover, undated (Box 162, Folder 27)
    - Fernandez, Julio
      - Adam Clayton Powell--Cover, 13 March 1967 (Box 167, Folder 7)
      - Hasser--Cover, 5 June 1967 (Box 167, Folder 8)
      - Milovan Djilas--Cover, 16 December 1968 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Geller, Barry
      - Untitled--Cover, 16 October 1961 (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - Japan, 27 November 1961 (Box 163, Folder 2)
      - John Kennedy--Cover, 22 January 1962 (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - Edwin A. Walke-Cover, 5 February 1962 (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - Untitled--Cover, 5 February 1962 (Box 163, Folder 5)
      - Lord Home, October 1963 (framed drawing) (Box 163, Folder 6)
      - Romulo Bentacourt, 11 November 1963 (framed drawing) (Box 163, Folder 7)
      - Untitled--Cover, 30 March 1964 (Box 163, Folder 8)
      - Untitled--Cover, 27 April 1964 (Box 163, Folder 9)
      - Barry Goldwater--Cover, 22 June 1964 (Box 163, Folder 10)
      - Untitled--Cover, 6 July 1964 (Box 163, Folder 11)
      - Brodsky Trial--Cover, 21 August 1964 (Box 163, Folder 12)
      - Kwame Nkrumah, 26 April 1965 (Box 163, Folder 13)
      - Houari Boumedienne--Cover, 30 August 1965 (Box 163, Folder 14)
      - Untitled, 31 January 1966 (Box 163, Folder 15)
      - Eduardo Frei--Cover, 23 May 1966 (Box 163, Folder 16)
      - Joaquin Balguer--Cover, 20 June 1966 (Box 163, Folder 17)
      - Mao--Cover, 30 January 1967 (Box 163, Folder 18)
      - Untitled--Cover, 27 March 1967 (Box 163, Folder 19)
      - Richard Lee--Mayor of New Haven--Cover, 11 September 1967 (Box 163, Folder 20)
      - Untitled--Cover, 6 November 1967 (Box 163, Folder 21)
      - Richard Nixon and Nelson Rockefeller, 11 March 1968 (Box 163, Folder 22)
      - Untitled--Cover, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 163, Folder 23 to 24)
    - Geller, Barry
      - Untitled, 18 September 1961 (Box 167, Folder 10)
      - Brigitte Bardot, 25 December 1961 (Box 167, Folder 11)
      - Untitled, 28 October 1963 (Box 167, Folder 12)
      - Ho Chi Minh--Cover, 3 January 1966 (Box 167, Folder 13)
      - Gustav Husak--Cover, 21 July 1969 (Box 167, Folder 14)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 167, Folder 15)
      - Untitled--Cover, 1968 (Box 167, Folder MD)
      - Untitled, undated (3) (Box 167, Folder MD)
    - Gersten, Gerry
      - Untitled--Cover, 22 July 1963 (Box 163, Folder 25)
      - Yitzak Rabin--Cover, 30 April 1974 (Box 163, Folder 26)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 163, Folder 27)
    - Gersten, Gerry
      - Covers
        - Untitled, 19 March 1962, (3 Folders) (Box 167, Folder 16 to 18)
        - Untitled, 2 April 1962 (Box 167, Folder 19)
      - John Mitchell, 15 October 1973 (Box 167, Folder 20)
      - The New Leader 50th Anniversary Caricatures
        - Daniel Bell, undated, framed (Box 167, Folder 21)
        - Kirkland, undated (Box 167, Folder 22)
        - Ralph Ellison, undated (Box 167, Folder 23)
        - Walter Mondale, Undated (Box 167, Folder 24)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 167, Folder 25)
    - Hering, Al
      - Ian Smith--Cover, 29 March 1976 (Box 163, Folder 28)
      - James Callaghan, undated (Box 163, Folder 29)
    - Holzman, D.--Untitled--Cover, 5 January 1970 (Box 163, Folder 30)
    - Kay--Untitled, 1969 (Box 163, Folder 31)
    - Kearns, J.--untitled, undated (Box 163, Folder md)
    - Kweskin, Sam
      - Konrad Adenaue--Cover, 8 January 1962 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - Untitled--Cover, 15 April 1963 (Box 164, Folder 2)
      - Untitled--Cover, 22 July 1963 (Box 164, Folder 3)
      - Guy Mollet, 25 November 1963 (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - Untitled--Cover, 6 January 1964 (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - J. William Fulbright--Cover, 13 April 1964 (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - Nikita Khrushchev--Cover, 25 May 1964 (Box 164, Folder 7)
      - Lyndon B. Johnson and Barry Goldwater--Cover, 20 July 1964 (Box 164, Folder 8)
      - Untitled--Cover, 19 October 1964 (Box 164, Folder 9)
      - Untitled--Cover, 27 September 1965 (Box 164, Folder 10)
      - [Louch] Whitlam, 22 January 1973 (Box 164, Folder 11)
      - Harold Geneen--ITT President, 16 April 1973 (Box 164, Folder 12)
      - Untitled--Cover, 28 May 1973 (Box 164, Folder 13)
      - Untitled--Cover, 9 July 1973 (Box 164, Folder 14)
      - Untitled--Cover, 24 December 1973 (Box 164, Folder 15)
      - Untitled--Cover, 1 April 1974 (Box 164, Folder 16)
      - Untitled--Cover, 11 November 1974 (Box 164, Folder 17)
      - Henry Jackso--Cover, 12 May 1975 (Box 164, Folder 18)
    - Kweskin, Sam
      - Harold Wilson--Cover, 8 July 1963 (Box 167, Folder 26)
      - Lyndon B. Johnson and John Kennedy--Cover, 9 December 1963 (Box 167, Folder 27)
    - Lincoln, Jay--Diane Sawyer, undated (Box 164, Folder 19)
    - Lubalin Smith Carnase--Untitled,--Cover, 14 June 1971 (Box 164, Folder 20)
    - Meintjies, J.E.
      - Karl Marx--Cover, 4 November 1968 (Box 165, Folder 1)
      - Richard M. Nixon, 18 November 1968 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Myers, Lou
      - Untitled, 8 January 1962 (Box 165, Folder 3)
      - Untitled, 30 April 1962 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Negron, Bill
      - Untitled--Cover, 13 November 1972 (Box 165, Folder 5)
      - Negron, Bill--Untitled--Cover, undated (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Shimon--Mihajlovich, 3 February 1975 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Shimon--[Valery Giscard P’Estang]--Cover, 6 January 1975 (Box 167, Folder 28)
    - Shore, Robert
      - Untitled--Cover, 23 July 1973 (Box 165, Folder 8)
      - Untitled--Cover, 3 September 1973 (Box 165, Folder 9)
      - Columbia University--Alma Mater--Cover, 8 July 1974 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Stevens, Elisabeth
      - Untitled--Cover, 15 October 1962 (Box 165, Folder 11)
      - Untitled--Cover, 1 February 1965 (Box 165, Folder 12)
      - Untitled--Cover, undated (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Stevens, Elisabeth--Untitled, undated (Box 167, Folder 29)
    - Sweetland, Ellen L.-- Hong Kong, undated (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Thompson, Mozelle, Untitled--Cover, 1 October 1962 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified
      - Charles de Gaulle, 16 October 1961 (Box 165, Folder 16)
      - John Kennedy, 16 October 1961 (Box 165, Folder 17)
      - Untitled--Cover, 19 March 1962 (Box 165, Folder 18)
      - Anibal Escalante, 16 April 1962 (Box 165, Folder 19)
      - Blas Roca--Cover, 16 April 1962 (Box 165, Folder 20)
      - Camilo Cienfuegos, 16 April 1962 (Box 165, Folder 21)
      - Untitled--Cover, 16 April 1962 cover (Box 165, Folder 22)
      - Untitled--Cover, 28 May 1962 (Box 165, Folder 23)
      - Untitled--Cover, 3 September 1962 cover (Box 165, Folder 24)
      - Newton Minow, 7 January 1963 (Box 165, Folder 25)
      - Hugh Gaitskell--Cover, 4 February 1963 (Box 165, Folder 26)
      - Untitled--Cover, 3 February 1964 (Box 165, Folder 27)
      - Untitled--Cover, 8 June 1964 (Box 165, Folder 28)
      - Soviet Union, 31 August 1964 (Box 165, Folder 29)
      - Untitled--Cover, 31 August 1964 (Box 165, Folder 30)
      - Untitled--Cover, 9 November 1964 (Box 165, Folder 31)
      - Benjamin Netanyahu--Cover, 1 February 1965 (Box 165, Folder 32)
      - Untitled--Cover, 12 April 1965 cover (Box 165, Folder 33)
      - Martin, Caamano, Trujillo, Imbert, Wessin, Bennett, 17 May 1965 (Box 165, Folder 34)
      - Untitled--Cover, 18 July 1966 (Box 165, Folder 35)
      - Eugene McCarth--Cover, 18 December 1967 (Box 165, Folder 36)
      - Untitled--Cover, 23 September 1968 (Box 165, Folder 37)
      - Untitled, undated (8) (Box 165, Folder MD)
      - Covers
        - Untitled, 24 November 1969 (Box 166, Folder 1)
        - Untitled, 2 March 1970 (Box 166, Folder 2)
        - Untitled, 8 June 1970 (Box 166, Folder 3)
        - Untitled, 7 August 1972 (Box 166, Folder 4)
        - Untitled, 25 November 1974 (Box 166, Folder 5)
        - Untitled, 20 January 1975 (Box 166, Folder 6)
        - The Road to Geneva, 23 June 1975 (Box 166, Folder 7)
      - Untitled, undated, (11 Folders) (Box 166, Folder 8 to 19)
    - Unidentified
      - Untitled, 30 October 1961 (Box 168, Folder 1)
      - Generalissimo Francisco Franco--Cover, 23 July 1962 (Box 168, Folder 2)
      - Untitled, 20 August 1962 (Box 168, Folder 3)
      - Untitled--Cover, 1 February 1965 (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - Untitled, 2 February 1970 (Box 168, Folder 5)
      - Jimmy Carter and Gerald Ford--Cover, 25 October 1976 (Box 168, Folder 6)
      - [Bill Clinton], undated (Box 168, Folder 7)
      - Charles de Gaulle, undated (Box 168, Folder 8)
      - Jean-Marie Le Pen, undated (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - Radovan [Karadzic], undated (Box 168, Folder 10)
      - Untitled, undated, (6 Folders) (Box 168, Folder 11 to 16)
      - Weston, Armand--Untitled--Cover, undated (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - Weisberg--Eldridge Cleaver--Cover, 16 February 1976 (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Weston, Armand
      - Covers
        - Untitled, 29 April 1963 (Box 166, Folder 21)